veoble.com 2016-06-16

# Veoble - Black Google Search

General

Veoble Search Engine is powered by Google. We filter only the relevant results from Google Search Engine. Therefore, you are also subject to Google Privacy. You may read it here: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you use our services. Our system automatically records information about your url, IP address, browser information, language and date and time that you visit our site. Any information we collect from you may be used to improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website services based on the information and feedback we receive from you.) and to measure the frequency of visitors (we analyze the data about visitors and our audience activity in our search engine).

For privacy purposes, we will not ask for your personal information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information and other important information about you. When you send email or other communication to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services. 

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure that the information that we get from you is kept safe and secured on our servers. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others` rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer`s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site`s or service provider`s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

Veoble is a search engine powered by Google. Google, a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google`s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on Dec. 09, 2012

Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Email: contact@veoble.com
